Thank you for watching!
Good morning.
Today, we are going to visit a
restaurant called Bachika.
We are going to visit this restaurant.
I have been thinking about what to do
for the day.
I have come up with a new idea.
A new idea?
I want to do it.
What is it?
You can't go home until you get the top
rank in the ranking of the restaurant.
I have heard of it.
I am not a man.
The title of this video is
You can't go home until you get the top
rank in the ranking of the restaurant.
You can't go home.
It is a new idea.
I think you don't know what it is
unless you explain it.
I don't know.
You can't go home until you get the top
rank in the ranking of the restaurant.
I see.
You can't go home until you finish
eating the food.
I see.
I am not sure if I am explaining it.
I don't know what it is.
I can see 2 seconds ahead.
This is a new idea.
You are smart.
I didn't know that.
I am surprised.
Let's order the menu.
I want to eat this.
I think it is common sense.
I think it is fried potato.
If it is not fried potato, I am not
sure.
Yuna has appeared on a program before.
I see.
Is there a special menu?
Yes, there is.
I have to change my plan.
There are potatoes in the menu.
I want to eat more.
It is popular.
This is a program.
I want to eat more.
I am sorry.
It is going to be long.
Shall we change the menu to vegetables?
That's good.
There is a pickled cucumber.
What do you like?
How about pickled cucumber?
I like it.
Shall we order?
I want to eat pickled cucumber.
Please.
Let's do our best.
Please subscribe to this channel.
What age group do you think will come?
I want to hear that.
People in their 30s to 60s.
People in their 40s to 60s.
I see.
I'm not good at it.
I want a soft one.
You are so greedy.
I got it.
Thank you.
I'll eat it with chopsticks.
I'll enjoy it.
I did it.
I can smell the flavor of the food.
It's delicious.
It's overwhelming.
I can taste the flavor.
I like the tea shop.
It was delicious.
It was really delicious.
I think I'm in the third place.
I think so.
I feel like I'm in the third place.
Let's go to the third place.
I'm in the third place.
You are not in the third place.
No way!
You don't eat it, do you?
You are not in the third place.
Really?
I eat 5 pieces of it at once.
It's so delicious.
It's really delicious.
You can't choose the next menu.
I see.
I've decided on the first one.
Massage.
I think I'm in the third place.
I'm in the third place.
Can I choose the massage?
Yes, you can.
Massage, please.
Death by Nae flavor?
Death by Nae flavor, condame flavor,
salt butter flavor.
It's a substitute.
I wonder what Yura is doing.
I wonder what she is doing.
The lighting is so calm that I feel
calm.
I know what you mean.
When the lighting is like this, I feel
like this.
I feel like I'm going to faint.
It's like tea.
There are many things.
The atmosphere and the lighting.
The lighting is important.
It's important.
Everyone is getting drunk.
When I see beautiful girls, I get
drunk.
I hate that.
I'm going to start singing.
I'm going to sing while I'm taking a
video.
I'm getting drunk.
We sang with our hands together.
Please subscribe to this channel!
Where is the sunset?
From the top.
What?
I'm curious.
The last one.
It's fast.
It looks delicious.
Is this...
Pony?
Pony.
Please suck it.
Thank you for the meal.
I've never eaten it.
Is it your first time?
What part is this?
Red meat.
I've never seen it.
The white part is the bone.
What?
Is this the bone?
It's the bone.
The red part is mixed.
The bone?
What are you doing?
It's the bone.
Thank you for the meal.
I'm scared.
It's my first time.
I'll put it on the tea.
It's hard.
It's my favorite.
It's delicious.
It's thick.
How is it?
It's mild.
It's delicious.
I'll finish eating.
I've finished eating.
Thank you for watching.
2nd place!
Yes!
I got it!
2nd place?
Wow!
I got 2nd place!
I want to talk about this.
It's all thanks to Yuna.
Yuna is recommending me.
I see.
Wow!
I'm so happy!
So, we have 4 left.
Yes.
Wow!
I love you.
What should I order?
What should we do?
I'm going to eat something light.
We can do it.
I want to eat something.
Yakisoba?
Yes, I want to eat Yakisoba.
I want to eat Yakisoba.
Yakisoba?
Yes, Yakisoba.
I feel good.
Yes.
I'm so happy!
Please subscribe to this channel.
Wow! I can see the egg!
It looks so good!
It's so big!
It's so smooth!
Happy birthday to you!
Happy birthday!
Please use this as a reference.
Let's eat!
It looks so good!
I did it!
It's so good!
Look at this!
It's so big!
It looks so good!
Let's eat!
It's a carrot cake.
It's so good!
Please subscribe to this channel.
I'm done.
Next, I'll eat Sosuyaki-Soba.
Sosuyaki-Soba.
It's Sosuyaki-Soba.
Sosuyaki-Soba with fried egg.
The order of fried egg is...
I'm sorry.
What?
You are lying.
You are a fool.
I'm sorry.
I'm a fool.
Really?
Let's move on.
The next is...
What?
It's a little thick.
100 points.
Let's eat.
Thank you for the meal.
What did you say?
It looks delicious.
It's delicious.
It's so soft and chewy.
It was great.
Thank you for the meal.
I think it's really in there.
The ranking of the fried potatoes is...
What?
Wait a minute.
What are you eating?
This is definitely...
This is out of the question, so let's
guess.
I agree.
Ham katsu...
I think ham katsu is in there.
I think it's the hottest ham katsu in
Japan.
I'm curious.
I'm wondering how hot it is.
I'm curious, too.
Ready, go.
The hottest ham katsu in Miyagi.
I'm confused.
Please subscribe!
It's a crab!
It's hot!
Look!
I love sauce!
Itadakimasu!
It's 3 pieces!
How long is it?
It's 5cm.
What?
If I had one more, it would be 10cm.
It's easy to carry.
I can tell it's 10cm.
I wonder how long it is.
It's heavy.
It's heavy, but it's good.
It's hot.
It's hot!
We finished it.
The best cutlet in Miyagi is...
5th place.
I feel relieved.
But it's 5th place.
I'm relieved.
The best cutlet in Miyagi is...
This is also fried egg.
It's easy to roll the stone.
It's cold and fun.
I'll do it with a spirit.
Let's do it.
The best cutlet in Miyagi is...
Fried egg.
I was motivated.
Let's eat.
It's sweet.
It's rich in flavor.
I like it.
Everything is delicious.
The last bite.
I'm relieved.
This is 7th place, isn't it?
I hope it's not.
The 10th place of the old-fashioned
Teppan Naporitan is...
This one.
I knew it! It's the center!
Everyone!
Wait a minute.
Thank you.
Thank you so much.
How many places are left?
3 places.
3 places?
3rd and 4th places are left.
3rd and 4th places?
It's enough.
I'll have the fried chicken, the grated
daikon radish and the ponzu sauce.
Thank you.
Please subscribe to the channel.
Let's eat fried chicken.
It's spicy.
It's a thin sliced pepper.
It smells good.
Let's eat.
It's good.
It's meat juice.
I think this is the best.
It's not the best.
It's the best.
It's good.
We finished eating.
Thank you for the meal.
It was good.
It's meat juice.
That's all for today.
Thank you for watching.
We ate all of them.
Please watch our video.
Bye bye.
The ranking announcement.
Please subscribe to the channel.
Go!
It's the first time I've heard that.
The first time I've heard that.
It's as big as my foot.
It looks delicious.
It looks like a pork cutlet.
It's a pork cutlet with a lot of pork.
It's good.
This is a pork cutlet.
It looks bigger than a pork cutlet.
Let's eat.
There's a lot of meat in it.
I like it.
I believe this is the sign.
It looks delicious.
It's crispy.
It's very delicious.
I'm happy.
Thank you for watching.
It's all delicious.
I'll do my best.
This is for everyone.
You're kind.
I'll eat it.
I'm going to eat it.
Thank you.
The winner is...
Sano!
I won!
Did you really line up the dishes in
order?
I just happened to do it.
It's a psychological game.
Next, let's eat the aburishime soba.
Yay!
The winner is...
Sano!
So, we ate 5 kaerema!
Each one of them was really good.
Please try them!
I like them.
I'm excited.
They are cute.
Please look forward to our next video!
Thank you!
I'm crying.
That's all!
Thank you for watching!
Bye-bye!
We ate special fried potato!
We are waiting for your comments!